Register of the Paul Robert Hanna Papers, 1920-1997
Hoover Institution Archives
- SUBJECT FILE, 1930-1982 (Boxes 41-129)
  - Department of Elementary School Principals, annual meeting, Miami Beach, request for visuals on social studies (Folder 10)
  - Dolby, James (Folder 11)
  - East-West Center
    - Alumni, 1975-1980 (Folder 12)
    - Bibliographies, 1964-65 (Folder 13)
    - Joint Seminar, East-West Center and Stanford International Development Education Center, 1967 (Folder 14)
    - Senior Specialist Program, January-June, 1965
      - Conference on Economic Planning in Southeast Asia, February 1-5, 1965 (Folder 15)
      - Conference on Economic Planning in Southeast Asia, February 1-5, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Contracts (Folder 2)
      - Housing (Folder 3)
      - Preliminary Prospectus (Folder 4)
      - Roster of Senior Specialists
        - January-June, 1965 (Folder 5)
        - 1965-66 (Folder 6)
      - Travel Arrangements (Folder 7)
  - Education
    - General (Folder 8-10)
    - China (Folder 11-12)
    - Spelling (Folder 13)
    - Spelling transparencies (Folder 14)
    - Spelling transparencies (Box 54, Folder 1-2)
  - Education and World Affairs
    - General (Folder 3)
    - "Brain Drain" papers, 1967 (Folder 4)
    - Committee on Content and Method, 1966 (Folder 5)
    - Committee on Education and Human Resource Development, 1964-68
    - Meetings
      - 1964
        - April 22, May 22 (Folder 6)
        - September 23 (Folder 7)
        - October 30 (Folder 8)
        - November 20 (Folder 9)
      - 1965
        - January 22-23 (Folder 10)
        - March 12 (Folder 11)
        - May 27 (Folder 12)
        - December 10 (Folder 13)
      - 1966
        - February 18 (Folder 14)
        - May 27 (Folder 15)
        - October 8 (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
        - December 19 (Folder 3)
      - 1967
        - March 3 (Folder 4)
        - May 19 (Folder 5-6)
        - August 20-23 (Folder 7-8)
        - October 27 (Folder 9)
      - 1968
        - March 29 (Box 56, Folder 1)
        - June (Folder 2)
        - July 24 (Folder 3)
    - Paper, "Education in the Service of Multinational Community Development," 1968 (Folder 4)
  - Eisner, Elliott, "The Curriculum Field Today: Where We Are, Where We Were and Where We Are Going," 1977 (Folder 4A)
  - Emigrant Gap Corporation, 1969-1970 (Folder 5)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica Films, Inc., 1954-57 (Folder 6-7)
  - Environmental Defense Fund (Folder 8)
  - Fellowship Forum, 1972-76 (Folder 9)
  - Fairlie, Henry, "Anti-Americanism at Home and Abroad," n.d. (Folder 9A)
  - Field Enterprises Educational Corporation, 1971-76 (Folder 10)
  - Ford Foundation
    - Correspondence, 1956-1963 (Folder 11)
    - Committee on University and World Affairs, meeting, Washington, D.C., March 23, 1961 (Folder 12)
    - Proposal for additional funding, Stanford Center for Educational Planning and International Development, 1965
      - March (Folder 13)
      - April (Folder 14)
    - Proposal for a World Network
      - Correspondence
        - General, 1963-66 (Box 57, Folder 1)
        - Baty, Harvey F., 1965 (Folder 2)
        - Carlson, Reynold E., 1963-64 (Folder 3)
        - de Carvalho, Laerte Ramos, 1964 (Folder 4)
        - Howard, John, 1965 (Folder 5)
      - Proposal
        - 1964-65, draft (Folder 6)
        - 1965
          - Draft (Folder 7)
          - Proposal no. 1 (Folder 8)
          - Proposal no. 2 (Folder 9-10)
      - Reactions to proposal, 1963-66 (Folder 11)
      - Submissions, 1964-65
    - Study of Post-War Educational Reform in Japan, University of Tokyo
      - Correspondence
        - May 1, 1958 -March 31, 1959 (Box 58, Folder 1)
        - April 1, 1959 -April 24, 1961 (Folder 2)
        - Everton, John, 1958-1964 (Folder 3)
      - Personnel, 1959 (Folder 4)
  - Forests and Forestry
    - General (Folder 5)
    - American Forestry Association, 1977-1980 (Folder 6)
    - American Forestry Institute, 1977-79 (Folder 7)
    - California Christmas Tree Growers (Folder 8)
    - California Department of Forestry
      - Resources Agency, 1977-79 (Folder 9)
      - Water storage tanks, 1978 (Folder 10)
    - California Farm Bureau (Folder 11)
    - California Forest Protection Agency
      - General, 1969-1975 (Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Folder 13)
      - Newsletters, 1975-76 (Folder 14)
    - California Redwood Association, 1978-79 (Folder 15)
    - California State Board of Forestry, 1977-1980 (Folder 16)
    - Conservation and planning (Folder 17)
    - Conservation and planning (Box 59, Folder 1-2)
    - Committee for Green Foothills (Folder 3)
    - Forest History Society, Inc. (Folder 4)
    - Forest Products Industry, 1973-77 (Folder 5)
    - Forest Products Research Society, 1979 (Folder 6)
    - Gazos Creek Tree Farms, 1978-1980 (Folder 7)
    - Mendocino County forestry, 1975-1980 (Folder 8)
    - National Association of Farmer-Elected Committeemen, 1976 (Folder 9)
    - New England Forestry Foundation, 1979 (Folder 10)
    - Oregon Forest Industry Council, 1978-1980 (Folder 11)
    - Peter Twight Associates, n.d. (Folder 12)
    - Redwood Region Conservation Council, 1975-1980 (Folder 13)
    - University of California-Berkeley, College of Natural Resources, Forest Products Laboratory, 1979-1980 (Folder 14)
    - Western Wood Products Association, 1971-76 (Folder 15)
  - Foundation for Teaching Economics, 1979-1980 (Folder 16)
  - Garcia, Marz, campaign, 1978 (Folder 17)
  - Governmental Research Council of San Mateo County
    - General
      - 1976-77 (Folder 18)
      - 1978 (Box 60, Folder 1-5)
      - 1979 (Folder 6-7)
      - 1979 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - 1980 (Folder 2-3)
      - 1981 (Folder 4-7)
      - 1982 (Box 62, Folder 1-2)
    - Analysis of the Fire Services System in San Mateo County, 1979 (Folder 3)
    - Committee on Parks and Recreation (Folder 4-5)
    - Forest management, 1980-81 (Folder 6-8)
    - Forest management, 1980-81 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Forest management study, 1980 (Folder 2)
    - "The Government Observer," 1976-1980 (Folder 3)
    - Public lands and facilities (Folder 4)
    - Merchant Marines (Folder 5)
  - Hamline University
    - General (Folder 6)
    - Commencement
      - 1979, program and copy of address by P.R. Hanna (Folder 7)
      - 1980 (Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1980 (Folder 9)
    - Gifts, 1977-79 (Folder 10)
    - "Prospectus for the Future," 1978 (Folder 11)
    - University Bulletin
      - April-May, 1976 (Folder 12)
      - October 1976, "Trees, Our Campus Wealth," by Paul R. Hanna (Folder 13)
  - Hamline University Alumni Association, 1968-1976 (Folder 14-15)
  - Hanna, Richard (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Hayden, Robert I. (Folder 2)
  - Heritage Foundation, 1977-1980 (Folder 3)
  - Highway beautification legislation, 1967 (Folder 4)
  - Hoover Institution
    - Miscellany (Folder 5)
    - Board of Overseers, 1976-1980 (Folder 6)
    - Educational Policy Group, possible members, 1980 (Folder 7)
    - Herbert Hoover Memorial Building, dedication, 1978-1980
      - General (Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, Oliver Fiennes, 1978-1980 (Folder 9)
      - Magna Carta display, 1979 (Folder 10)
  - Houghton Mifflin Company
    - Editorial Advisory Committee for College Books in Education (Folder 11)
    - Geography textbook project
      - Miscellany (Folder 12)
      - Contract, 1964 (Folder 13)
      - Correspondence
        - General, 1965-69 (Folder 14)
        - Davies, Gordon, 1964-66 (Folder 15)
        - Farrar, Charles, 1964-66 (Folder 16)
        - MacDonald, William D., 1964-68 (Folder 17)
        - Saberoff, Rose, 1964-1967 (Folder 18)
      - Promotional material, n.d. (Folder 19)
      - Publisher's Editorial Advisory Committee in Education
        - Contract, 1964 (Folder 20)
        - Correspondence
          - 1964-1966 (Box 65, Folder 1)
          - 1967 (Folder 2)
          - 1968 (Folder 3)
    - Spelling textbook project
      - Miscellany (Folder 4-5)
      - Computer code sheets, computer cards, and related matter, 1969 (Folder 6)
      - Contracts, 1932-1969 (Folder 7)
      - Copyright registration and renewal certificates, 1947-1975 (Folder 8)
      - Correspondence
        - 1933 (Folder 9)
        - 1934 (Folder 10)
        - 1935 (Folder 11)
        - 1936 (Box 66, Folder 1)
        - 1937 (Folder 2)
        - 1938 (Folder 3)
        - 1939 (Folder 4)
        - 1940 (Folder 5)
        - 1941 (Folder 6)
        - 1942 (Folder 7)
        - 1943 (Folder 8)
        - 1944 (Folder 9)
        - 1945 (Folder 10)
        - 1946-1950 (Folder 11)
        - 1951-53 (Folder 12)
        - 1954 (Folder 13)
        - 1955 (Folder 14)
        - 1956 (Folder 15)
        - 1957 (Box 67, Folder 1)
        - 1958 (Folder 2)
        - 1959 (Folder 3)
        - 1960 (Folder 4)
        - 1961 (Folder 5)
        - 1962
          - January-June (Folder 6)
          - July-December (Folder 7)
        - 1963 (Box 68, Folder 1)
        - 1964
          - January-June (Folder 2)
          - July-December (Folder 3)
        - 1965
          - January-June (Folder 4)
          - July-December (Folder 5)
        - 1966
          - January-March (Folder 6)
          - April-June (Box 69, Folder 1)
          - July-December (Folder 2)
        - 1967
          - January-February (Folder 3)
          - March-June (Folder 4)
          - July-December (Folder 5)
        - 1968
          - January-March (Box 70, Folder 1)
          - April-June (Folder 2)
          - July-December (Folder 3)
        - 1969
          - January-March (Folder 4)
          - April-June (Folder 5)
          - July-September (Folder 6)
          - October-December (Folder 7)
        - 1970
          - January-June (Box 71, Folder 1-2)
          - July-December (Folder 3)
        - 1972 (Folder 4)
        - 1973-1982 (Folder 5)
      - Drafts
        - Undated (Folder 6-7)
        - Undated (Box 72, Folder 1)
        - 1945 (Folder 2)
        - ca. 1955-56 (Folder 3-5)
        - 1962 (Folder 6)
        - 1963 (Folder 7)
      - Galleys, 1956 (Folder 8)
      - Lists of vocabulary words (Folder 9)
      - Notes
        - Undated (Folder 10)
        - 1947-1948 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Promotional materials
        - General (Folder 2)
        - Campaigns
          - 1959-1969 (Folder 3)
          - California campaigns, 1972-74 (Folder 4)
          - Texas campaigns, 1959-1960 (Folder 5)
        - Brochures, pamphlets, advertisements, 1935-1969 (Folder 6-7)
        - Overhead visuals (Folder 8)
        - Overhead visuals (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Reprints, 1953-1966 (Folder 2)
      - Reviews, 1968-1971 (Folder 3)
      - Schedule, summer, 1969 (Folder 4)
      - Supplementary materials (Folder 5)
      - Texts, 1943, 1967 (Folder 6-8)
  - Huntley, James R. (Folder 9)
  - Infomedica, Inc., 1973-1974 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Institute for Gifted Youth (proposed), correspondence, John Gardner, 1979 (Folder 2)
  - International Council on Education for Teaching, 1973-74 (Folder 3)
  - International Institute for Educational Planning, Paris (Folder 4)
  - International Journal of Political Education (Folder 5)
  - John Dewey Society
    - General (Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1956-1974 (Folder 7)
    - Publications, 1968-1975 (Folder 8)
  - Kappa Delta Pi, 1976-1980 (Folder 9)
  - Kellogg Foundation
    - Miscellany (Folder 10)
    - Annual Report, 1948-49 (Folder 11)
    - Correspondence
      - General, 1944-49 (Folder 12)
      - Faris, Ruby, 1949 (Folder 13)
      - Masters, Hugh B., 1944-1959 (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - Mawby, Russell G., 1979 (Folder 2)
      - Morris, Emory, 1944-1965 (Folder 3)
      - Seay, Maurice, 1944-1964 (Folder 4)
      - White, Leonard, 1978-1980 (Folder 5)
    - "The First Half-Century, Private Approaches to Public Needs," 1930-1980 (Folder 6)
    - Meetings
      - 1944
        - General (Folder 7)
        - June 5-7 (Folder 8)
      - 1945
        - March 30-April 3 (Folder 9)
        - September 4-7 (Folder 10)
      - 1948, July 26-28 (Folder 11)
      - 1949, June 31 (Folder 12)
      - 1954
        - January 13-15 (Folder 13)
        - December 5-7 (Folder 14)
      - 1956, June 20-23 (Folder 15)
      - 1957, May 22-23 (Folder 16)
      - 1959
        - July 2-25 (Folder 17)
        - September 12-13 (Folder 18)
    - "Profiles," 1978, Vol. l, Nos. 1-2 (Folder 19)
    - Projects and proposals
      - General (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - 1940-45, Community Health and Recreation Centers (Folder 2)
      - 1944, Rural Education at Stanford University (Folder 3)
      - 1954, National Agricultural Center for Advanced Study (Folder 4)
      - 1955-58, Stanford University Center for Continuing Education (Folder 5)
      - 1956, Stanford University Center for Student Activities (Folder 6)
      - ca. 1959, Stanford University Study of Administrative Personality and Behavior (Folder 7)
      - 1966-67, San Diego Camping Education Project (Folder 8)
  - Kirst, Michael W., Curriculum: A Key to Improving Academic Standards," May 1981 (Folder 9A)
  - Lake Shastina
    - Correspondence, 1970-74 (Folder 9)
    - Maps and Brochures, 1973 (Folder 10)
    - Newsletters, 1970-74 (Folder 11)
  - Law and Order Campaign Committee (Folder 12)
  - Lee, Richard V. (Folder 12A)
  - Lee L. and David Jacks Professorships of Education, Stanford University
    - General
      - 1943-46 (Folder 13)
      - 1954-55 (Folder 14)
    - Higher Education Search Committee, 1965-66 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Installation ceremonies, 1954 (Folder 2)
  - League to Save Lake Tahoe, 1969-1974 (Folder 3)
  - Learning theory
    - General (Folder 4)
    - Gonda, T.A., "Psychiatry," reprint, Annual Review of Medicine, Vol. 10, 1959 (Folder 5)
    - Harvard University, Center for Cognitive Studies, Annual Report, 1961 (Folder 6)
    - Kellogg Foundation proposal, laws of learning (Folder 7)
    - Laws of learning (Folder 8-9)
    - "Learning Theory and Our Schools," conference, 1960 (Folder 10)
    - "Man and Civilization: Control of the Mind," UC SF Medical Center, 1961-62 (Folder 11)
    - Pribram, Karl H.
      - "Interrelations of Psychology and the Neurological Disciplines," June 1957 (Folder 12)
      - "Neocortical Function in Behavior," March 1955 (Folder 13)
      - "On the Neurology of Thinking," reprint, Behavioral Science, Vol. 4, No. 4, October 1959 (Folder 14)
      - "A Review of Theory in Physiological Psychology," reprint, Annual Review of Psychology, Vol. II, 1960 (Folder 15)
      - "Toward a Science of Neuropsychology," n.d. (Folder 16)
    - Pribram, Karl H. and Lawrence Kruger, "Functions of the Olfactory Brain," reprint, Annals of the New York Academy of Sciences, Vol. 58, March 24, 1954 (Folder 17)
  - Library of Congress, correspondence, 1977 (Folder 18)
  - Linus Pauling Institute of Science and Medicine, 1980 (Folder 19)
  - McTaggart, Bernice (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Magna Research, Inc.
    - Miscellany (Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1961, 1969 (Folder 3)
    - Products
      - Magna Center, 1969 (Folder 4)
      - Creative Adventure Series, 1969 (Folder 5)
    - Publication, Darrell Huff, How to be the Parent of a Successful Creative Child, 1969 (Folder 6)
  - Mali, proposed contract, 1963 (Folder 7)
  - Margaret Jacks Professorship of Education, Stanford University, 1954-1970 (Folder 8)
  - Mary Jacks Thomas Fund, Stanford University
    - Charges
      - 1955-1958 (Folder 9)
      - 1958-1966 (Folder 10)
    - Orders and Charges
      - 1954-September 24, 1961 (Folder 11)
      - September 25, 1961-August 31, 1963 (Folder 12)
      - September 1, 1963-August 31, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - September 1, 1964-August 31, 1965 (Folder 2)
  - Mary Jacks Thomas Fund, Stanford University
    - Supplies and expenses
      - June 30, 1954-August 31, 1958 (Folder 3)
      - September 1, 1958-August 31, 1963 (Folder 4)
  - Michigan State Department of Education, consulting, 1968-1970 (Folder 5)
  - Morgan, B.Q. and F.W. Strothmann, "Report on Postwar Reconstruction in Germany," n.d. (Folder 6)
  - The Nation, 1959 (Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Education, 1975-1980 (Folder 8)
  - National Association of Elementary School Principals, 1979-1980 (Folder 9-10)
  - National Association of Property Owners (Folder 11)
  - National Commission on Coping with Interdependence
    - General (Folder 12-13)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Folder 14)
    - Publications (Folder 15)
  - National Council for the Social Studies
    - Correspondence, Hunnicutt, C.W., 1956-57 (Folder 16)
    - Meetings
      - November 23-25, 1961 (Folder 17)
      - November 25-28, 1964 (Folder 18)
    - Permission to reprint material (Folder 19)
    - Yearbook, 1958-1962 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - National Council of the Foreign Policy Association (Folder 2)
  - National Education Association
    - General (Folder 3)
    - McLendon, Jonathan C., "Teaching the Social Studies," April 1960 (Folder 4)
  - National Historical Society, 1980 (Folder 5)
  - National Planning Association, 1973 (Folder 6)
  - National Republican Senatorial Committee, 1977 (Folder 7)
  - National Right To Work Committee, 1977 (Folder 8)
  - National Society For The Study of Education, 1965-1979 (Folder 9-10)
  - National Tax Limitation Committee, 1978-1980 (Folder 11)
  - National Taxpayers' Union (Folder 12)
  - NEA Reporter, 1979 (Folder 13)
  - Netter, Frank H., The Central Nervous System, 1949 (Folder 14)
  - "New Right Report," 1978 (Folder 15)
  - Northern California Coastal Events Calendar, 1980 (Folder 16)
  - Northern Trust for Historic Presenvation, 1971-1981 (Folder 17)
  - Off-Road vehicles (Folder 18)
  - Organization of American Historians, 1980 (Folder 19)
  - Organizations
    - American Association for State and Local History (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - American Association of School Administrators (Folder 2)
    - American Forest Institute (Folder 3)
    - American Institute for Economic Research (Folder 4)
    - American Security Council (Folder 5)
    - Americans Against Union Control of Government (Folder 6)
    - Americans for Nuclear Energy (Folder 7)
    - Aspen Institute (Folder 8)
    - Associated Building Industry of Northern California (Folder 9)
    - Association for Supervision and Curriculum Development (Folder 10)
    - Association of Bay Area Governments (Folder 11)
    - Atlantic Council (Folder 12)
    - Bureau of Intelligence and Research (Folder 13)
    - California Coastal Council (Folder 14)
    - California Conservation Zone Commission (Folder 15-16)
    - California History Center Foundation (Folder 17)
    - California Parks and Recreation (Folder 18)
    - California Republican Assembly (Folder 19)
    - California Taxpayers Association (Folder 20)
    - Center for International Security Studies (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Coalition of Concerned Citizens (Folder 2)
    - Committee for Economic Development (Folder 3)
    - Common Cause (Folder 4)
    - Conservation and planning
      - Redwood Region Conservation Council
        - Correspondence, 1970-76 (Folder 5)
        - Speaking engagement, February 4, 1972 (Folder 6)
      - Scenic highways, Santa Cruz mountains (Folder 7)
    - Education, general (Folder 8)
    - Educational Policies Commission (Folder 9)
    - Environmental Action (Folder 10)
    - Environmental Defense Fund (Folder 11)
    - Federal Union (Folder 12)
    - Forest History Society (Folder 13)
    - Forest Industries Committee on Timber Valuation and Taxation (Folder 14)
    - Forest Landowners of California (Folder 15-16)
    - Fraternities
      - Kappa Delta Pi (Folder 17)
      - Theta Chi (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Friends of Arnett (Folder 2)
    - Golden Gate Recreation Authority (Folder 3)
    - International Council on Education for Teaching (Folder 4)
    - James T. Watkins IV Discretionary Fund (Folder 5)
    - National Right to Work Committee (Folder 6)
    - Thomas Jefferson Research Center (Folder 7)
    - Wilderness Alert (Folder 8)
    - World Affairs Council of Northern California (Folder 9)
    - World Research, Inc. (Folder 10)
  - "The Outlook," September-November 1980 (Folder 11)
  - Pacific Legal Foundation, 1977-1980 (Folder 12)
  - Palo Alto Senior Coordinating Council, 1977 (Folder 13)
  - Peace Corps
    - General, 1967-69 (Folder 14)
    - Manual and bibliography of research, 1968 (Folder 15)
  - Peace Corps, University of Hawaii Study Committee
    - General, 1969 (Folder 16)
    - Miscellany (Folder 17)
    - Correspondence
      - 1968 (Folder 18)
      - 1969
        - January-June (Box 85, Folder 1)
        - July-December (Folder 2)
      - 1970 (Folder 3)
    - Expenses, 1968-69 (Folder 4)
    - Meetings, 1968
      - January 17-19, Palo Alto, California (Folder 5)
      - November 12-13, Washington, D.C. (Folder 6)
      - December 13-22, Hilo, Hawaii (Folder 7)
      - Minutes, November-December, 1968 (Folder 8)
    - Reports
      - Miscellaneous, 1968-69 (Folder 9-11)
      - "The Peace Corps and the University: A Report of the Special Committee to Study Peace Corps/University Relations," February 1969 (Box 86, Folder 1-2)
  - Peninsula Open Space Trust, 1978 (Folder 3)
  - Pescadero Community Council, 1980 (Folder 4)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1976-1980 (Folder 5)
  - Phi Delta Kappa, 1977-1980 (Folder 6)
  - Phonetics
    - General (Folder 7-8)
    - Berquist, Sidney, "An Heuristic Analysis of the Structure of America-English Orthography: Phase III-An Index of Liguistic Complexity," dissertation proposal, Stanford University, 1964 (Folder 9)
    - Hodges, Richard E., "An Heuristic Analysis of the Structure of America-English Orthography: Phase I--An Analysis of the Phonological Structure," dissertation proposal, Stanford University, 1964 (Folder 10)
    - Rudorf, Edwin H.
      - "An Heuristic Analysis of the Structure of America-English Orthography: Phase II--the Development of Heuristics," dissertation proposal, Stanford University, 1964 (Folder 11)
      - The Development of an Algorithm For American-English Spelling, dissertation, Stanford University, 1964 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - "Spelling Demon Witchhunt," n.d. (Folder 2)
    - U.S. Department of Education, Project 1991
      - General (Folder 3)
      - Budget, expenses, supplies, and personnel, 1962-65 (Folder 4)
      - Budget, expenses, supplies, and personnel, 1962-65 (Box 88, Folder 1)
      - Coding, keypunching, and processing
        - General (Folder 2)
        - Bids from contractors, 1963 (Folder 3)
        - Contracts, 1962-64
          - Control Data Corporation, 1963 (Folder 4)
          - Service Bureau Corporation, 1963 (Folder 5)
          - Stanford University, 1962-64 (Folder 6)
      - Correspondence
        - 1961-63 (Folder 7)
        - 1964-66 (Folder 8)
        - 1968-1971 (Folder 9)
        - Berquist, Sidney, 1964-66 (Folder 10)
        - Carroll, John B., 1962-64 (Folder 11)
        - Control Data Corporation, 1963-66 (Folder 12)
        - Dewey, Godfrey, 1963-66 (Folder 13)
        - Dolby, J.C., 1963-66 (Folder 14)
        - Gunderson, Doris, 1963-66 (Folder 15)
        - Hodges, Richard, 1963-66 (Folder 16)
        - Horn, Ernest, 1963-64 (Box 89, Folder 1)
        - Horn, Thomas, 1963-67 (Folder 2)
        - Rudorf, Edwin H., 1961-65 (Folder 3)
        - Scates, Alice Y., 1963-64 (Folder 4)
        - Soloman, Herbert, 1962-65 (Folder 5)
        - Strickland, Ruth, 1962-64 (Folder 6)
        - Trager, Edith Crowell, 1962-63 (Folder 7)
      - Notes
        - Computer Analysis (Folder 8)
        - Talks (Folder 9)
      - Pilot study, 1963 (Folder 10)
      - Progress reports, 1963-64 (Folder 11)
      - Proposals, U.S. Office of Education
        - November 1961 (Box 90, Folder 1)
        - March 1962 (Folder 2)
        - August 29 and December 11, 1962 (Folder 3)
      - Writings, Hanna et al.
        - "A Summary: Linguistic Cues for Spelling Improvement," 1963-64 (Folder 4)